<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Containers>
  <Date>2022-02-20</Date>
  <Beta>False</Beta>
  <Category></Category>
  <Name>Freqtrade</Name>
  <Project>https://freqtrade.io/</Project>
  <Changes/>
  <Overview>
    Freqtrade is a crypto-currency algorithmic trading software developed in python (3.8+) and supported on Windows, macOS and Linux.
  </Overview>
  <Description>
    Freqtrade is a crypto-currency algorithmic trading software developed in python (3.8+) and supported on Windows, macOS and Linux.
    [b]Features[/b]
    Develop your Strategy: Write your strategy in python, using pandas. Example strategies to inspire you are available in the strategy repository.
    Download market data: Download historical data of the exchange and the markets your may want to trade with.
    Backtest: Test your strategy on downloaded historical data.
    Optimize: Find the best parameters for your strategy using hyperoptimization which employs machining learning methods. You can optimize buy, sell, take profit (ROI), stop-loss and trailing stop-loss parameters for your strategy.
    Select markets: Create your static list or use an automatic one based on top traded volumes and/or prices (not available during backtesting). You can also explicitly blacklist markets you don't want to trade.
    Run: Test your strategy with simulated money (Dry-Run mode) or deploy it with real money (Live-Trade mode).
    Run using Edge (optional module): The concept is to find the best historical trade expectancy by markets based on variation of the stop-loss and then allow/reject markets to trade. The sizing of the trade is based on a risk of a percentage of your capital.
    Control/Monitor: Use Telegram or a REST API (start/stop the bot, show profit/loss, daily summary, current open trades results, etc.).
    Analyse: Further analysis can be performed on either Backtesting data or Freqtrade trading history (SQL database), including automated standard plots, and methods to load the data into interactive environments.
  </Description>
  <Registry>https://registry.hub.docker.com/r/freqtradeorg/freqtrade</Registry>
  <GitHub>https://github.com/freqtrade/freqtrade</GitHub>
  <Repository>freqtradeorg/freqtrade</Repository>
  <Support></Support>
  <BindTime>true</BindTime>
  <Privileged>true</Privileged>
  <Networking>
    <Mode>host</Mode>
    <Publish/>
  </Networking>
  <Environment>
    <Variable>
      <Value>/freqtrade/user_data/logs/freqtrade.log</Value>
      <Name>LOGFILE</Name>
      <Mode/>
    </Variable>
    <Variable>
      <Value>sqlite:////freqtrade/user_data/tradesv3.sqlite</Value>
      <Name>DB_URL</Name>
      <Mode/>
    </Variable>
    <Variable>
      <Value>/freqtrade/user_data/config.json</Value>
      <Name>CONFIG</Name>
      <Mode/>
    </Variable>
    <Variable>
      <Value>SampleStrategy</Value>
      <Name>STRATEGY</Name>
      <Mode/>
    </Variable>
  </Environment>
  <Data>
    <Volume>
      <HostDir>/mnt/user/appdata/freqtrade</HostDir>
      <ContainerDir>/freqtrade</ContainerDir>
      <Mode>rw</Mode>
    </Volume>
    <Volume>
      <HostDir>/mnt/user/appdata/freqtrade/user_data</HostDir>
      <ContainerDir>/freqtrade/user_data</ContainerDir>
      <Mode>rw</Mode>
    </Volume>
  </Data>
  <WebUI>http://[IP]:[PORT:8080]</WebUI>
  <Banner></Banner>
  <Icon>https://www.freqtrade.io/en/stable/images/logo.png</Icon>
</Containers>
